jeep.com.au 2016-03-25

# 

## CHRYSLER AUSTRALIA PTY LTD trading as FIAT CHRYSLER GROUP  
(Chrysler, Jeep, Dodge, Fiat, Alfa Romeo, Fiat Professional, Abarth, Mopar and SRT)  
Version Date: March 2014

### INTRODUCTION

Welcome to this Chrysler Australia Pty Ltd ("CA") website. CA is a member of the worldwide Fiat Chrysler Group ("FCG"), a group of companies comprising Chrysler Group LLC and Fiat Group Automobiles S.p.A. and all their associated companies.

### PRIVACY STATEMENT

CA respects privacy and Personal Information and wants to give you comfort we take this issue seriously. Where CA deals with your Personal Information, being an Australian company, CA is governed by and complies with the Australian Privacy Principles ("APPs") set out in Schedule 1 of the Privacy Amendment (Enhancing Privacy Protection) Act 2012 which will be incorporated into the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (as amended from time to time) ("Privacy Act") from 12 March 2014. The APPs replace the National Privacy Principles and the Information Privacy Principles.

We know that you care about how your Personal Information is collected, used, and shared and we want to help you make knowledgeable choices about the information you provide to us. This Privacy Statement ("Privacy Statement") explains and summarizes how CA collects, uses, and protects your information, including the Personal Information that you may provide to us or that we may collect from you as you interact with us.

This Privacy Statement applies when CA collects data from customers and guests, including through CA controlled websites or applications, and CA controlled applications accessed and/or used on a mobile, handheld or other wirelessly connected device (a "Website" or "Application"). Any Personal Information you provide is voluntary. "Personal Information" includes information that alone or when in combination with other information may be used to readily identify, contact, or locate you (e.g., name, address, telephone number, email address, and location).

By disclosing your Personal Information to us or using our Websites or Applications, you consent to its collection, use and distribution by CA consistent with applicable data protection and other relevant laws and this Privacy Statement (which is expressly incorporated into any applicable Website or Application terms of use).

We will update this Privacy Statement from time to time, so please check back with us periodically, as your continued use of our Websites or Applications means you acknowledge, agree to and consent to those changes.

### WHY WE COLLECT YOUR INFORMATION AND HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

CA collects and uses your Personal Information to provide information relating to our products and services that is relevant to your interests. We also collect your Personal Information to:

  * respond to your requests for information relating to sales, quotes, our products, brochures, test drives and services offered;
  * respond to feedback, complaints or a comments whether made by electronic means, telephone or in person;
  * supply products and services to you;
  * allow you to use E Commerce when you purchase a product on-line and process and collect payment and deal with your account when you purchase products or services from us or our dealers;
  * communicate with our dealers to organise and allow you to test drive our cars or get a quote;
  * to pass on enquiries or complaints made by you regarding our products, sales or services to a dealer or a related party of CA who can assist with your enquiry or complaint;
  * purchase goods and services from you;
  * manage vehicle warranties;
  * product registration and support;
  * keep track of repairs to your vehicle;
  * effect product recalls;
  * provide after sale customer support such as issue service reminders and roadside assist;
  * improve the quality of our service by contacting you to determine your level of customer satisfaction;
  * provide dealer support;
  * notify you periodically about important things like an update to an Application or our terms and conditions;
  * undertake marketing and promotional activities;
  * provide you with direct marketing to inform you of special offers and promotions that we think may be of interest to you;
  * conduct market research and product development;
  * contact you in the event of a security breach;
  * meet our internal reporting requirements within the FCG in relation to statistics on sales, warranties, repairs and marketing;
  * process employment applications;
  * report to and evaluate dealers;
  * engage contractors;
  * meet our legal and regulatory responsibilities and for fraud prevention purposes such as verifying your identity; 
  * allow you to benefit from combining your location data with location based functionality in our Website and Applications, for example to locate your closest dealer or get a quote locally;
  * contact you by email, phone, SMS or MMS or in any other lawful manner for the purposes set out above.

CA does not collect and process any Personal Information unless the information is considered necessary for the effective functioning or activities of our business. Because most of the information is collected directly from you or indirectly from information you have given to a dealer, you will normally be aware of the purpose of its collection.

Generally, CA only processes Personal Information for the purposes for which it was originally collected being the primary purposes stated above, unless required or authorised by or under law or if the individual concerned has consented to the intended use.

### DIRECT MARKETING

When you provide your Personal Information such as an address, email address and/or phone number you are consenting to receive direct marketing material from CA and our related bodies corporate by way of phone calls, mail, email, SMS text messages, mobile message services MMS or instant messaging.  
We do disclose Personal Information to third parties to allow them to direct market our products and services to you in the ways described above. The types of third parties that may contact you with direct marketing are set out below in Other Information Uses and Disclosure to Third Parties. There are times when we join with dealers and other business associates of CA and may undertake joint marketing of our respective products and services to you.

If you wish to opt out of receiving any direct marketing you may unsubscribe from these emails by clicking on the link within the email or by advising us by sending an email to: [marketingau@chrysler.com](mailto:marketingau@chrysler.com), by phone by calling 03 8698 0200 or by mail to Direct Marketing Manager, Chrysler Australia Pty Ltd, 437 Plummer Street, Port Melbourne, Vic, 3207.

### HOW WE COLLECT YOUR INFORMATION 

In the course of providing services to you, CA collects your information in a number of ways.

For example, we collect information when you:

  * use this website to make an enquiry about our products and services such as when you request to be sent information or for purposes that are made clear on the page on which the information is collected;
  * are employed by us through the application and employment process, including through third parties such as your referees and previous employers;
  * enter our website our third party Internet Host provider records your server address; domain name, the date and time of your visit and the pages viewed;
  * Google analytics;
  * enter into written agreements with us, our dealers, agents or third party service providers;
  * purchase a vehicle or service a vehicle and become a customer;
  * supply goods or services to us;
  * answer a survey or respond to requests from a market research agencies engaged by us;
  * fill in a competition form;
  * post a comment on our website, send us an email or make a telephone enquiry;
  * ask to be placed on a mailing list;
  * provide your information to a third party that we supply or provide services to such as our Group related body corporates, dealers and distributors, contractors and regulatory authorities.

CA may also collect information about you that is publicly available from outside sources including information from telephone directories, the electoral roll, other websites, device ID information from mobile applications or advertisements or purchase e-mail or similar lists from third parties for advertising and marketing purposes.

### TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT

The types of information we collect include:

  * Name, email address, telephone and fax numbers and delivery details;
  * Drivers' Licence details;
  * Age;
  * Gender;
  * Occupation;
  * ABN;
  * Your car registration details, VIN and number plate;
  * Your car's repairs and service history;
  * IP Address;
  * Location Data;
  * Device type (iPhone, laptop etc);
  * domain name;
  * Web browser, Safari, Firefox;
  * Date and time of access to the website and which website you came from;
  * Content of emails;
  * information you post on your webpage.

Location Data and other information that you provide to us or that may be accessed in connection with your use of such a CA Website or Application. Your use of, and our ability to offer location based functionality is then enabled through our use and disclosure to third parties of Location Data and associated information. E-Commerce. When you interact with us or purchase a CA product online (for example, to get a quote or locate a dealer) you will be asked for information needed to complete your request. The information you provide is used, for example, to process your transactions, to create and share reports about these transactions, or to provide related customer service. When you shop online or buy direct from one of our online stores, these purchase transactions may be conducted through CA vendors and suppliers.

### CUSTOMER'S SENSITIVE INFORMATION

CA does not generally require customers to provide sensitive information such as race, religious beliefs, sexual orientation or health information etc.

Occasionally a customer will advise a disability or a trade or professional association that is sensitive information but we do not actively seek this information. If you disclose sensitive information you consent to our collecting, using and disclosing this sensitive information for the purpose for which you disclosed it to us and as permitted under the Privacy Act and other relevant laws.

### CONTRACTOR TO CA

If you are a contractor to CA we may collect information relating to your engagement by CA in relation to your qualifications, training records and logs, references, length of engagement, resume, pay rate, salary, bank account details and ABN.

### EMPLOYMENT APPLICATIONS

If you apply for a job with CA we will use the Personal Information you provide to assess your application. We may disclose your Personal Information to third party service providers to assist with the assessment which may include screening, aptitude tests, human resources management purposes such as background checks and discussing your application with referees, medical tests and health assessments.

During this process we may collect sensitive Personal Information which is provided directly by you. The sensitive information that may be collected during the employment process if given voluntarily by you includes: tax file numbers, race, religion, professional or trade association memberships, health or criminal records. As part of the application, we may ask you to undergo a medical assessment and/or complete a health questionnaire. If this occurs we may disclose your Personal Information to a third party service provider for the purposes of completing a health/medical assessment. If a health/medical assessment is required, we will ask for your consent again at the time we need to make the disclosure. If you are unable to consent to these disclosures we will not be able to consider your application for employment.

CA does not collect and/or process any personal or sensitive information against the express wishes of an individual, unless CA is required by law to do so.

### ANONYMITY AND PSEUDONYMS

You have the right to remain anonymous or use a pseudonym when entering into transactions with CA, unless such anonymity or use of a pseudonym would be considered unlawful or impracticable. Please let us know if you wish to deal with us anonymously or by a pseudonym.

Failing to provide your Personal Information may in some instances make it impractical or impossible to provide you with our products or services. For example, if we are unable to collect your Personal Information at the time of a new vehicle purchase, we would not be able to notify you of a product recall affecting your vehicle and would not be able to register the transfer of ownership with the licensing authority.

### NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION, COOKIES, AND RELATED INFORMATION COLLECTION

CA or others acting on our behalf may use cookies, pixel tags, web beacons or other similar technologies in connection with the operation of our Websites or Applications. These technologies may collect and store non-Personal Information. We utilize these technologies to research and understand how our Websites and Applications are used, to develop our products and services, to personalize your online experience with CA and for general advertising and marketing purposes. We may share data collected from you on our Websites with our third party vendors or suppliers to advertise or market to you on other sites as you browse the web. At the end of your visit, session cookies used by CA are removed. However, in some instances some CA cookies may persist. For example, to customize your experience we may require registration to recognize your computer and enable you to log-in without having to enter your password. It is possible that Cookies placed by CA or its vendors or suppliers (as applicable) in connection with the operation of the Website or Application may remain stored on your computer until you remove them.

Our service providers or vendors may also use cookies and related technologies in order to personalize your experiences and adapt a particular FCG Website or Application's functionality to your preferences and for purposes such as those listed above. If you are visiting a URL other than the FCG websites (www.chrysler.com.au, www.jeep.com.au, www.dodge.com.au, www.fiat.com.au, www.alfaromeo.com.au, www.abarth.com.au, www.fiatcommercial.com.au, www.mopar.com.au, www.cjddealer.com.au, www.fiatalfadealer.com.au) or other CA or FCG Websites or Applications, you should carefully review the privacy policies of those web sites or applications.

You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to refuse receiving it. You should be aware that this may interfere with or make you unable to use certain functionality on websites using cookies and you may not be able to take full advantage of the services available to you on our website. For example, many websites will ask your permission to use a cookie that will enable you to automatically log onto the website. Disabling or removing cookies may require you to manually log on each time you wish to visit that website.

### OTHER INFORMATION USES AND DISCLOSURE TO THIRD PARTIES

CA does not use or pass onto others any Personal Information without the consent of the individual(s) concerned and as disclosed in this privacy policy or unless required by law.

CA's third party service providers may occasionally have access to the Personal Information held by CA under conditions of confidentiality.

Our third party service providers are only authorised to use the information for the purpose for which we supply the information. Examples of the types of third parties we may need to disclose information to in the course of providing a product or service are:

  * related bodies corporate of CA;
  * CA dealers;
  * CA partners or their respective related bodies corporate;
  * employees and contractors;
  * parts suppliers;
  * web hosting, data housing providers and other IT suppliers;
  * insurers, lawyers, financiers and other professional advisers;
  * outsourcing to a service provider engaged by CA to provide a particular service on CA's behalf such as: 
    * printers of our marketing material;
    * mailing houses to bulk mail marketing and promotional material,
    * agencies that deal with product recalls and send information to affected customers; and
    * marketing and research agencies that assist us with promotions or competitions, market research and trend analysis;
  * entities that provide roadside assistance to the purchasers of our vehicles and membership to autoclubs;
  * entities that process credit card payments;
  * Vehicle licensing authorities;
  * Tax Office.
  * a Court or to a third party under a subpoena issued by a Court;
  * a regulatory authority;
  * law enforcement purposes.

CA may be required to disclose personal consent without consent of the individual where the law requires us to make the disclosure to bodies such as:

  * Tax Office;
  * a Court or to a third party under a subpoena issued by a Court;
  * a regulatory authority.

CA may use information relating to your visit to our website, or information you provide to us, for market research purposes in order to continually improve the products and services that CA delivers to you.

On occasions, CA may form relationships with other organisations, designed to bring you special offers or competitions, relevant to your preferences. CA only deals with parties that demonstrate the same level of commitment to your privacy as CA does, and can assure complete compliance with all Australian privacy laws.

Certain promotions may be run by a CA service provider or vendor or co-branded with one of our partners or run on a third party site like Facebook. In these instances the collection of your Personal Information may occur directly by the service provider or vendor or a third-party partner on their website. The promotion will state the policies governing the collection of such information if they should differ from this Privacy Statement.

Vendors and suppliers engaged by CA may have their use of your Personal Information limited by this Privacy Statement, contractual restrictions, or applicable law. However, if a particular Website or Application is co-branded or developed by a third party, it is possible that another party's Privacy Statement will govern the treatment of information on that Website or Application. CA (through its vendors or suppliers) may limit the acceptance of orders to particular jurisdictions and as permitted by applicable law.

CA may sometimes permit our authorized service providers to have access to aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related Website or Application information. These transfers of aggregate statistics do not involve Personal Information.

Enabling Services. CA offers a variety of services and functions through its Websites and Applications. Personal Information that is collected through a Website or Application may be used and/or disclosed to third parties in order to enable us to provide functionality or services to you. For example, some CA Websites and Applications allow you to interface with third party websites or applications. To facilitate that connection, we may use your Personal Information and/or disclose your Personal Information to third parties. When we provide location based services enabled through a third party, we may share data with those services in order to provide the related location based service or functionality.

### MERGERS, ACQUISITIONS, AND INSOLVENCY

If CA should ever file for bankruptcy or in the unlikely event that CA reorganizes or sells a part or the whole of its business or merges with another entity, its records of Personal Information may be transferred to a prospective purchaser, the actual purchaser, an entity a party to the merger or released to a liquidator. The information will remain subject to privacy laws and until further notified, will remain subject to CA's privacy policy.

### COMMUNICATION OPT OUT OPTIONS

If at any stage you are receiving communications from CA and you do not wish to receive any further communications, please let us know by contacting us in one of the following ways:

Email:  
By mail: 

Addressed to: Direct Marketing Manager  
Chrysler Australia Pty Ltd  
437 Plummer Street  
Port Melbourne Vic 3207 

### TRANSFER OF INFORMATION OVERSEAS

CA as part of the FCG has internal reporting requirements to other FCG entities. Other FCG entities may also provide a range of technology, operational (such as database storage services) and customer service functions on CA's behalf which may involve the transfer of your Personal Information to other FCG entities located overseas. If you are an employee or contractor your personnel records, which may contain sensitive Personal Information may be sent overseas to other FCG entities and/or FCG database storage services.

Some of our third party service providers to whom we disclose Personal Information to may also be located outside Australia.

The countries we may send your information to include: Italy, Singapore, China, United States and India.

Except where an exception applies under the Privacy Act, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that such overseas recipients do not breach the privacy principles of the Privacy Act in relation to Personal Information.

### ACCURACY OF INFORMATION

CA takes all reasonable steps to ensure that Personal Information is accurate, up to date, complete, relevant and is not misleading. To assist us in making sure your Personal Information is accurate, up to date and complete, we may contact you from time to time to ask you to advise us of any changes to your Personal Information. If you discover any Personal Information we hold about you is incorrect, please contact us immediately and we will correct it. The contact details to correct Personal Information should be directed to the Chief Security Officer of CA whose details are set out under Access to your Personal Information and Further Questions.

If after receipt of your request to correct information we refuse to do so, you may request we associate the information with a statement that the information is incorrect, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading. If we refuse to correct your information we will provide you with reasons for the refusal and the mechanisms available to you to complain about the refusal.

### SECURITY OF INFORMATION

CA takes all reasonable steps to ensure that Personal Information is kept safe from misuse, interference, loss and unauthorised access, modification and disclosure. The electronic database that holds the information is designed to restrict access to unauthorised persons.

No data transmissions over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Consequently, CA cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to CA and you do so at your own risk. Once CA receives your transmission, CA makes reasonable efforts to ensure security on our systems. CA uses secure server software (SSL) and firewalls to protect your information from unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of such firewalls and secure server software. If CA learns of a security system's breach, CA may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using this website or providing Personal Information to CA, you agree that CA can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of this website. CA may send an email to you at the email address you have provided to CA if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing.

Except to the extent liability cannot be excluded under statute, we exclude all liability (including in negligence) for the consequences of any unauthorised access to, disclosure of, misuse of or loss or corruption of your Personal Information. Nothing in this privacy policy restricts, excludes or modifies or purports to restrict, exclude or modify any statutory consumer rights under any applicable law including the Competition and Consumer Act 2010 (Cth). If you become aware of any breach of security involving your Personal Information, please contact us immediately.

The internet is not secure and Personal Information you send to us via the internet is done so at your own risk.

CA takes all reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify Personal Information that is no longer needed for a permitted purpose and it is not required to be retained by law.

### PUBLIC AREAS

Any information disclosed in public areas of a CA Website or Application or other website (Facebook, YouTube, Twitter, etc.) will become public information. CA cannot control the use of information disclosed in public forums, such as social media forums, platforms, bulletin boards, blogs, wikis, chat rooms, and networking functions of mobile-device applications. You should exercise caution when disclosing information in these public areas, especially your location-data, and be careful how you disclose your Personal Information. Content posted in public areas of CA Websites or Applications, including advice and opinions, represent the views and is the responsibility of those who post the content. CA does not necessarily endorse, support, verify, or agree with the content posted and reserves the right to remove comments that CA considers to be offensive, derogatory or otherwise inappropriate. If you have any questions or comments about any content on a CA Website or Application please send us an email: [marketingau@chrysler.com](mailto:marketingau@chrysler.com).

### CHILDREN

FCG Websites and Applications are not directed at children. If you are under 18 or otherwise would be required to have parent or guardian consent to share information with CA, you should not send any information about yourself to CA. If a person under 18 submits information through any part of a FCG Website or Application, and CA learns the person submitting the information is a child, CA will attempt to delete this information as soon as possible. Because CA does not knowingly collect any Personal Information from persons under 18, CA does not knowingly use or disclose such information to third parties.

### ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, FURTHER QUESTIONS AND COMPLAINTS

At all times, CA strives to ensure your Personal Information is treated confidentially, and in accordance with the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). If you believe your Personal Information has been handled in a way that does not comply with the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth), or if you wish to access information that CA holds about you, please contact us.

For security reasons, we require that requests for Personal Information are provided in writing. Please provide as much detail as possible in relation to your question, concern or complaint to help us assist you. CA will endeavour to provide you with this access unless CA is required or authorised to refuse such access by the laws of Australia. All such enquiries should be directed to:

Chief Security Officer  
Chrysler Australia Pty Ltd  
437 Plummer Street, Port Melbourne, VIC 3207. Australia  
PO Box 23267, Dockland 3008  

Our Chief Security Officer will investigate your complaint, concern or query in a timely and efficient manner and will seek to resolve the issue directly with you.

We may charge you a fee for accessing your Personal Information which will reflect our reasonable costs of retrieving and supplying the information to you.

We may refuse to give you access to your information and if we do so, will give written reasons for the refusal together with the mechanisms available to complain about the refusal. We can refuse access where the information relates to anticipated legal proceedings, the request is frivolous or vexatious or giving access would have an unreasonable impact on the privacy of other individuals.

### COPYRIGHTS

The text, images, graphics, sound files, animation files, video files and their arrangement on this CA website are all subject to copyright and other intellectual property protection laws in Australia and other countries, including but not limited to the Copyright Act 1968 (Cth) and through international treaties. Apart from any use that is permitted under the Copyright Act 1968 (Cth) all rights are reserved. These objects may not be copied for commercial use or distribution, nor may these objects be modified or reposted to other Internet sites. Some CA sites also contain images that are subject to the copyright rights of third party providers.

### DIGITAL MILLENNIUM COPYRIGHT ACT ("DMCA") POLICY

CA respects the intellectual property rights of others. Materials may be posted and made available on this Website by third parties not within our control. It is our policy not to permit materials known by us to be infringing to remain on the website and to terminate the accounts of third parties who repeatedly infringe the copyrights of others.  
If you believe that any material on the website infringes your copyright, you should provide us with written notice that, at a minimum, contains the following information:

  1. Identification of the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed, or, if multiple copyrighted works found on the Website are covered by a single notification, a representative list of such works found on the Website;
  2. Identification of the material that is claimed to be infringing or to be the subject of infringing activity and that is to be removed or access to which is to be disabled, and information reasonably sufficient to permit us to locate the material;
  3. Information reasonably sufficient to permit us to contact you, including your address, telephone number, and if available, your e-mail address;
  4. A statement that you have a good faith belief that the use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, the owner's agent or the law;
  5. A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that you are authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed; and
  6. A physical or electronic signature of a person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.

All DMCA notices should be sent to our designated copyright agent as follows:

Chrysler Group LLC  
Office of the General Counsel  
Copyright Department  
1000 Chrysler Drive  
CIMS 485-13-32  
Auburn Hills, MI 48326 U.S.A.  

### TRADE MARKS

This site includes registered trade marks, trade marks which are the subject of pending applications and trade marks which are otherwise protected by law. Unless otherwise indicated, all trade marks displayed on this CA Website and any Application are subject to the trade mark rights of FCG. These include each of the FCG's primary brands and products (Chrysler, Jeep®, Dodge, Fiat, Alfa Romeo, Fiat Professional, Abarth, Mopar, SRT and Chrysler Financial), and the model name plates, corporate logos and emblems of the FCG.

### PRODUCT VARIATIONS

Some of the product information illustrations and images contained on this site may have been prepared for generic use on sites that are maintained in different countries around the world. Consequently, some of the information and/or accessories may not be available in some countries or may, in order to satisfy local market demand or regulatory controls, only be available in different specifications or configurations. If you are interested in any vehicle model, paint, option or accessory shown on this site and are unsure of its availability or specification in your locality, you should contact CA or your local authorised Chrysler, Jeep, Dodge, Fiat, Alfa Romeo, Fiat Professional, Abarth, Mopar or SRT dealer for the relevant product or brand, including information of current details and options available in your locality.

### PRICES

All prices specified are, unless otherwise specified, recommended maximum driveaway prices, inclusive of all government charges and dealer delivery costs. Prices are current at the time of publication and are subject to change at any time and from time to time without notice.

### NO WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS

The information that is contained on this site is for preliminary and general purposes only. CA may at any time and from time to time at its full and complete discretion make any changes to the information that is contained in this site. This information is provided by CA "as is" and to the extent permitted by law, is provided without warranty of any kind, expressed or implied, including (but not limited to) any implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for any particular purpose, or non-infringement. While the information provided is believed to be accurate, it may include errors or inaccuracies. As such, no reliance whatsoever should be placed on the information that is contained in this site as being accurate, complete and up to date. CA is not responsible for and will not accept responsibility for any cost, damage, expense or loss (whether direct or indirect) that is or may be incurred as a result of any possible error, misrepresentation and or omission that is, was, or may be contained in this site at any time and from time to time.

### NO LICENSES

CA has sought to achieve an innovative and informative site. We hope that you will be as enthusiastic as we are about this creative effort. However, you also need to understand that the FCG must protect its intellectual property, including its patents, trade marks and copyrights. Accordingly, you are hereby on notice that neither this site, nor any material contained therein shall in any way grant or be taken to grant any person a licence to the FCG's intellectual property.

### LINKS TO OTHER SITES

This site may contain links to other Internet sites that are owned by third parties. These links are provided solely for your convenience and do not indicate either express or implied endorsement by CA of the products or services that are provided by that Internet site. When accessing third party Internet sites and using those products and services you agree and undertake to do so at your own risk as CA is not responsible for and cannot control the privacy practices of these other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies for these other websites, as they may differ from ours. **These terms and conditions apply solely to Personal Information collected by CA on its Websites and Applications.**
